https://sonaearauco.secure.force.com/sind/grpdmanageprivacysettings

Error
Javascript is not enabled in this browser.
Please enable Javascript in your browser settings or use a different browser.
Welcome to Sonae Arauco
The privacy of your data is important to us
In order to access your privacy profile, consult your personal data and verify the purpose for which it is used, please enter your email to receive an access link and an identity verification code.
Send email
Thank you for your trust.
The privacy of your data is important to us
lockPlease verify your identity
Please, confirm your identity, by entering the verification code that was sent to you by email:
Verify
Alternatively, you can also access directly by using the link that was sent to you in the same email.
If you have not received any email (it may take a few minutes) or you are having difficulty accessing the link, please contact us at dataprotection@sonaearauco.com
errorUnable to find your records...
Looks like your details are not in our database.
If you have any questions, please contact Sonae Arauco´s Data Protection team at dataprotection@sonaearauco.com.
Go back
Welcome to your privacy profile
Protecting your data is important to us
...
Your Consent check
Your Personal Data person_outline
To be clear about the way Sonae Arauco takes care of your data, please see Information to the personal data owner
In order to continue to communicate and keep you informed of Sonae Arauco´s marketing actions, we need your informed and explicit consent.
I confirm I have read the Information to the personal data owner
I give permission to Sonae Arauco to process my personal data for the purpose of marketing initiatives:
Please choose:
Yes
No
Confirm
To be clear about the way Sonae Arauco takes care of your data, please see Information to the personal data owner
To update / confirm your personal data, please use the form below:
First name
Last name
Title
Function
Department
Email
Phone
Mobile phone
Ethiopia
Falkland Islands (Malvinas)
Faroe Islands
Fiji
Finland
France
French Guiana
French Polynesia
French Southern Territories
Gabon
Heard Island and McDonald Islands
Holy See (Vatican City State)
Honduras
Hungary
Iceland
India
Indonesia
Iran, Islamic Republic of
Iraq
Ireland
Saint Lucia
Saint Martin (French part)
Saint Pierre and Miquelon
Saint Vincent and the Grenadines
Samoa
San Marino
Sao Tome and Principe
Saudi Arabia
Senegal
Serbia
Seychelles
Sierra Leone
Singapore
Sint Maarten (Dutch part)
Slovakia
Slovenia
Solomon Islands
Somalia
South Africa
South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands
South Sudan
Spain
Save
Thank you for continuing with us on this trip!
Your privacy options were successfully updated.
With your consent, we can continue to communicate and inspire you with the most innovative proposals and solutions.
Whenever you wish, you can access and update your personal data through the link that was sent to you by email or at your Privacy Profile at www.sonaearauco.com
If you have any questions, please contact Sonae Arauco´s Data Protection team at dataprotection@sonaearauco.com
Continue to Sonae Arauco website
We are sorry to see you go.
However, if you wish, you may review your privacy options and change your decision:
Change consent
If you have any questions, please contact Sonae Arauco´s Data Protection team at dataprotection@sonaearauco.com
Continue to Sonae Arauco website
Thanks for confirming your data!
Whenever you wish, you can access and update your personal data through the link that was sent to you by email or at your Privacy Profile at www.sonaearauco.com
If you have any questions, please contact Sonae Arauco´s Data Protection team at dataprotection@sonaearauco.com
